{
  "title": "AZ-900 Azure Fundamentals",
  "description": "Microsoft Azure Fundamentals - 203 Questions",
  "totalQuestions": 203,
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "original_number": "2",
      "question": "Your company has datacenters in Los Angeles and New York. The company has a Microsoft Azure subscription.You are con+guring the two datacenters as geo-clustered sites for site resiliency.You need to recommend an Azure storage redundancy option.You have the following data storage requirements:✑ Data must be stored on multiple nodes.✑ Data must be stored on nodes in separate geographic locations.✑ Data can be read from the secondary location as well as from the primary locationWhich of the following Azure stored redundancy options should you recommend?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Geo-redundant storage"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Read-only geo-redundant storage"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Zone-redundant storage"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Locally redundant storage"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "RA-GRS allows you to have higher read availability for your storage account by providing ג€read onlyג €access to the data replicated to thesecondary location. Once you enable this feature, the secondary location may be used to achieve higher availability in the event the data is notavailable in the primary region. This is anג€opt-inג €feature which requires the storage account be geo-replicated. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/storage/common/storage-redundancy"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "original_number": "3",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.Your company's Azure subscription includes a Basic support plan.They would like to request an assessment of an Azure environment's design from Microsoft. This is, however, not supported by the existing plan.You want to make sure that the company subscribes to a support plan that allows this functionality, while keeping expenses to a minimum.Solution: You recommend that the company subscribes to the Professional Direct support plan.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/support/plans"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "original_number": "4",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.You are tasked with deploying Azure virtual machines for your company.You need to make use of the appropriate cloud deployment solution.Solution: You should make use of Software as a Service (SaaS).Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "original_number": "5",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.You are tasked with deploying Azure virtual machines for your company.You need to make use of the appropriate cloud deployment solution.Solution: You should make use of Platform as a Service (PaaS).Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "original_number": "6",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.You are tasked with deploying Azure virtual machines for your company.You need to make use of the appropriate cloud deployment solution.Solution: You should make use of Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS).Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "original_number": "7",
      "question": "Your developers have created 10 web applications that must be host on Azure.You need to determine which Azure web tier plan to host the web apps. The web tier plan must meet the following requirements:✑ The web apps will use custom domains.✑ The web apps each require 10 GB of storage.✑ The web apps must each run in dedicated compute instances.✑ Load balancing between instances must be included.✑ Costs must be minimized.Which web tier plan should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Standard"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Basic"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Free"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Shared"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Standard offers 50 GB of storage space, while Basic only gives 10 GB. | Reference: http://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/pricing/details/websites"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "original_number": "8",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.You are planning to migrate a company to Azure. Each of the company's numerous divisions will have an administrator in place to manage theAzure resources used by their respective division.You want to make sure that the Azure deployment you employ allows for Azure to be segmented for the divisions, while keeping administrativeeffort to a minimum.Solution: You plan to make use of several Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) directories.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "original_number": "9",
      "question": "Your developers have created a portal web app for users in the Miami branch ohce. The web app will be publicly accessible and used by theMiami users to retrieve customer and product information. The web app is currently running in an on-premises test environment.You plan to host the web app on Azure.You need to determine which Azure web tier plan to host the web app. The web tier plan must meet the following requirements:✑ The website will use the miami.weyland.com URL.✑ The website will be deployed to two instances.✑ SSL support must be included.✑ The website requires 12 GB of storage.✑ Costs must be minimized.Which web tier plan should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Standard"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Basic"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Free"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Shared"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Reference: http://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/documentation/articles/azure-subscription-service-limits"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "original_number": "10",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.Your company is planning to migrate all their virtual machines to an Azure pay-as-you-go subscription. The virtual machines are currently hostedon the Hyper-V hosts in a data center.You are required make sure that the intended Azure solution uses the correct expenditure model.Solution: You should recommend the use of the elastic expenditure model.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "original_number": "11",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.Your company is planning to migrate all their virtual machines to an Azure pay-as-you-go subscription. The virtual machines are currently hostedon the Hyper-V hosts in a data center.You are required make sure that the intended Azure solution uses the correct expenditure model.Solution: You should recommend the use of the scalable expenditure model.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "original_number": "12",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.Your company is planning to migrate all their virtual machines to an Azure pay-as-you-go subscription. The virtual machines are currently hostedon the Hyper-V hosts in a data center.You are required make sure that the intended Azure solution uses the correct expenditure model.Solution: You should recommend the use of the operational expenditure model.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "original_number": "13",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.You are required to deploy an Arti+cial Intelligence (AI) solution in Azure.You want to make sure that you are able to build, test, and deploy predictive analytics for the solution.Solution: You should make use of Azure Cosmos DB.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "original_number": "14",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.Your company's Active Directory forest includes thousands of user accounts.You have been informed that all network resources will be migrated to Azure. Thereafter, the on-premises data center will be retired.You are required to employ a strategy that reduces the effect on users, once the planned migration has been completed.Solution: You plan to sync all the Active Directory user accounts to Azure Active Directory (Azure AD).Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "original_number": "15",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.You are required to deploy an Arti+cial Intelligence (AI) solution in Azure.You want to make sure that you are able to build, test, and deploy predictive analytics for the solution.Solution: You should make use of Azure Machine Learning Studio.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "original_number": "16",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.Your company's infrastructure includes a number of business units that each need a large number of various Azure resources for everydayoperation.The resources required by each business unit are identical.You are required to sanction a strategy to create Azure resources automatically.Solution: You recommend that the Azure API Management service be included in the strategy.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "original_number": "17",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.Your company's infrastructure includes a number of business units that each need a large number of various Azure resources for everydayoperation.The resources required by each business unit are identical.You are required to sanction a strategy to create Azure resources automatically.Solution: You recommend that management groups be included in the strategy.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "original_number": "18",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.Your company's infrastructure includes a number of business units that each need a large number of various Azure resources for everydayoperation.The resources required by each business unit are identical.You are required to sanction a strategy to create Azure resources automatically.Solution: You recommend that the Azure Resource Manager templates be included in the strategy.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "original_number": "19",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.You are tasked with deploying a critical LOB application, which will be installed on a virtual machine, to Azure.You are informed that the application deployment strategy should allow for a guaranteed availability of 99.99 percent. You need to make sure thatthe strategy requires as little virtual machines and availability zones as possible.Solution: You include two virtual machines and one availability zone in your strategy.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/availability-zones/az-overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "original_number": "20",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.You are tasked with deploying a critical LOB application, which will be installed on a virtual machine, to Azure.You are informed that the application deployment strategy should allow for a guaranteed availability of 99.99 percent. You need to make sure thatthe strategy requires as little virtual machines and availability zones as possible.Solution: You include one virtual machine and two availability zones in your strategy.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/availability-zones/az-overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "original_number": "21",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.You are tasked with deploying a critical LOB application, which will be installed on a virtual machine, to Azure.You are informed that the application deployment strategy should allow for a guaranteed availability of 99.99 percent. You need to make sure thatthe strategy requires as little virtual machines and availability zones as possible.Solution: You include two virtual machines and two availability zones in your strategy.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/availability-zones/az-overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "original_number": "22",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.Your company's developers intend to deploy a large number of custom virtual machines on a weekly basis. They will also be removing thesevirtual machines during the same week it was deployed. Sixty percent of the virtual machines have Windows Server 2016 installed, while the otherforty percent has Ubuntu Linux installed.You are required to make sure that the administrative effort, needed for this process, is reduced by employing a suitable Azure service.Solution: You recommend the use of Microsoft Managed Desktop.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "original_number": "23",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.Your company's developers intend to deploy a large number of custom virtual machines on a weekly basis. They will also be removing thesevirtual machines during the same week it was deployed. Sixty percent of the virtual machines have Windows Server 2016 installed, while the otherforty percent has Ubuntu Linux installed.You are required to make sure that the administrative effort, needed for this process, is reduced by employing a suitable Azure service.Solution: You recommend the use of Azure Reserved Virtual Machines (VM) Instances.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "original_number": "24",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.Your company's developers intend to deploy a large number of custom virtual machines on a weekly basis. They will also be removing thesevirtual machines during the same week it was deployed. Sixty percent of the virtual machines have Windows Server 2016 installed, while the otherforty percent has Ubuntu Linux installed.You are required to make sure that the administrative effort, needed for this process, is reduced by employing a suitable Azure service.Solution: You recommend the use of Azure DevTest Labs.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "original_number": "25",
      "question": "Your company has virtual machines (VMs) hosted in Microsoft Azure. The VMs are located in a single Azure virtual network named VNet1.The company has users that work remotely. The remote workers require access to the VMs on VNet1.You need to provide access for the remote workers.What should you do?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Con+gure a Site-to-Site (S2S) VPN."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Con+gure a VNet-toVNet VPN."
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Con+gure a Point-to-Site (P2S) VPN."
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Con+gure DirectAccess on a Windows Server 2012 server VM."
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "Con+gure a Multi-Site VPN"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "A Point-to-Site (P2S) VPN gateway connection lets you create a secure connection to your virtual network from an individual client computer. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/vpn-gateway/vpn-gateway-about-vpngatewaysCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "original_number": "26",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.You have been informed by your superiors of the company's intentions to automate server deployment to Azure. There is, however, some concernthat administrative credentials could be uncovered during this process.You are required to make sure that during the deployment, the administrative credentials are encrypted using a suitable Azure solution.Solution: You recommend the use of Azure Information Protection.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "original_number": "27",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.You have been informed by your superiors of the company's intentions to automate server deployment to Azure. There is, however, some concernthat administrative credentials could be uncovered during this process.You are required to make sure that during the deployment, the administrative credentials are encrypted using a suitable Azure solution.Solution: You recommend the use of Azure Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA).Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "original_number": "29",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.Your company has an Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) environment. Users occasionally connect to Azure AD via the Internet.You have been tasked with making sure that users who connect to Azure AD via the internet from an unidenti+ed IP address, are automaticallyencouraged to change passwords.Solution: You con+gure the use of Azure AD Identity Protection.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/active-directory/identity-protection/howto-sign-in-risk-policyCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "original_number": "30",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.Your company has an Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) environment. Users occasionally connect to Azure AD via the Internet.You have been tasked with making sure that users who connect to Azure AD via the internet from an unidenti+ed IP address, are automaticallyencouraged to change passwords.Solution: You con+gure the use of Azure AD Privileged Identity Management.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/active-directory/identity-protection/howto-sign-in-risk-policyCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "original_number": "31",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.You are planning a strategy to deploy numerous web servers and database servers to Azure.This strategy should allow for connection types between the web servers and database servers to be controlled.Solution: You include network security groups (NSGs) in your strategy.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "original_number": "32",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.You are planning a strategy to deploy numerous web servers and database servers to Azure.This strategy should allow for connection types between the web servers and database servers to be controlled.Solution: You include a local network gateway in your strategy.Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "original_number": "33",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.Establish if the solution satis+es the requirements.Your company's Active Directory forest includes thousands of user accounts.You have been informed that all network resources will be migrated to Azure. Thereafter, the on-premises data center will be retired.You are required to employ a strategy that reduces the effect on users, once the planned migration has been completed.Solution: You plan to require Azure Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA).Does the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "original_number": "37",
      "question": "You have an on-premises network that contains several servers.You plan to migrate all the servers to Azure.You need to recommend a solution to ensure that some of the servers are available if a single Azure data center goes oline for an extendedperiod.What should you include in the recommendation?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "fault tolerance"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "elasticity"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "scalability"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "low latency"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machines/windows/manage-availabilityCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "original_number": "39",
      "question": "What are two characteristics of the public cloud? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.NOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "dedicated hardware"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "unsecured connections"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "limited storage"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "metered pricing"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "self-service management"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "EWith the public cloud, you get pay-as-you-go pricing ג \"€you pay only for what you use, no CapEx costs.With the public cloud, you have self-service management. You are responsible for the deployment and con+guration of the cloud resourcessuch as virtual machines or web sites. The underlying hardware that hosts the cloud resources is managed by the cloud provider.Incorrect Answers:A: You don't have dedicated hardware. The underlying hardware is shared so you could have multiple customers using cloud resources hostedon the same physical hardware.B: Connections to the public cloud are secure.C: Storage is not limited. You can have as much storage as you like. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-gb/learn/modules/principles-cloud-computing/4-cloud-deployment-modelsCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "original_number": "41",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.Your company plans to migrate all its data and resources to Azure.The company's migration plan states that only Platform as a Service (PaaS) solutions must be used in Azure.You need to deploy an Azure environment that meets the company migration plan.Solution: You create an Azure App Service and Azure SQL databases.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Azure App Service and Azure SQL databases are examples of Azure PaaS solutions. Therefore, this solution does meet the goal."
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "original_number": "42",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.Your company plans to migrate all its data and resources to Azure.The company's migration plan states that only Platform as a Service (PaaS) solutions must be used in Azure.You need to deploy an Azure environment that meets the company migration plan.Solution: You create an Azure App Service and Azure virtual machines that have Microsoft SQL Server installed.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Azure App Service is a PaaS (Platform as a Service) service. Azure virtual machines are an IaaS (Infrastructure as a Service) service, and aPaas service.Therefore, this solution does meet the goal.Note: Like IaaS, PaaS includes infrastructureג\"€servers, storage, and networkingג\"€but also middleware, development tools, businessintelligence (BI) services, database management systems, and more. PaaS is designed to support the complete web application lifecycle:building, testing, deploying, managing, and updating. | Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-paas"
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "original_number": "43",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.Your company plans to migrate all its data and resources to Azure.The company's migration plan states that only Platform as a Service (PaaS) solutions must be used in Azure.You need to deploy an Azure environment that meets the company migration plan.Solution: You create an Azure App Service and Azure Storage accounts.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "original_number": "44",
      "question": "Your company hosts an accounting application named App1 that is used by all the customers of the company.App1 has low usage during the +rst three weeks of each month and very high usage during the last week of each month.Which bene+t of Azure Cloud Services supports cost management for this type of usage pattern?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "high availability"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "high latency"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "elasticity"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "load balancing"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Elasticity in this case is the ability to provide additional compute resource when needed and reduce the compute resource when not needed toreduce costs.Autoscaling is an example of elasticity.Elastic computing is the ability to quickly expand or decrease computer processing, memory and storage resources to meet changing demandswithout worrying about capacity planning and engineering for peak usage. Typically controlled by system monitoring tools, elastic computingmatches the amount of resources allocated to the amount of resources actually needed without disrupting operations. With cloud elasticity, acompany avoids paying for unused capacity or idle resources and doesn't have to worry about investing in the purchase or maintenance ofadditional resources and equipment. | Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/overview/what-is-elastic-computing"
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "original_number": "45",
      "question": "You plan to migrate a web application to Azure. The web application is accessed by external users.You need to recommend a cloud deployment solution to minimize the amount of administrative effort used to manage the web application.What should you include in the recommendation?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Software as a Service (SaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Platform as a Service (PaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Database as a Service (DaaS)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Azure App Service is a platform-as-a-service (PaaS) offering that lets you create web and mobile apps for any platform or device and connect todata anywhere, in the cloud or on-premises. App Service includes the web and mobile capabilities that were previously delivered separately asAzure Websites and Azure MobileServices. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/security/fundamentals/paas-applications-using-app-servicesCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "original_number": "47",
      "question": "You have an on-premises network that contains 100 servers.You need to recommend a solution that provides additional resources to your users. The solution must minimize capital and operationalexpenditure costs.What should you include in the recommendation?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a complete migration to the public cloud"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an additional data center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a private cloud"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a hybrid cloud"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-gb/learn/modules/principles-cloud-computing/4-cloud-deployment-modelsCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "original_number": "49",
      "question": "You plan to migrate several servers from an on-premises network to Azure.What is an advantage of using a public cloud service for the servers over an on-premises network?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "The public cloud is owned by the public, NOT a private corporation"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "The public cloud is a crowd-sourcing solution that provides corporations with the ability to enhance the cloud"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "All public cloud resources can be freely accessed by every member of the public"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "The public cloud is a shared entity whereby multiple corporations each use a portion of the resources in the cloud"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "original_number": "51",
      "question": "In which type of cloud model are all the hardware resources owned by a third-party and shared between multiple tenants?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "private"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "hybrid"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "public"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Microsoft Azure, Amazon Web Services and Google Cloud are three examples of public cloud services.Microsoft, Amazon and Google own the hardware. The tenants are the customers who use the public cloud services."
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "original_number": "53",
      "question": "You have 1,000 virtual machines hosted on the Hyper-V hosts in a data center.You plan to migrate all the virtual machines to an Azure pay-as-you-go subscription.You need to identify which expenditure model to use for the planned Azure solution.Which expenditure model should you identify?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "operational"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "elastic"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "capital"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "scalable"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "One of the major changes that you will face when you move from on-premises cloud to the public cloud is the switch from capital expenditure(buying hardware) to operating expenditure (paying for service as you use it). This switch also requires more careful management of yourcosts. The bene+t of the cloud is that you can fundamentally and positively affect the cost of a service you use by merely shutting down orresizing it when it's not needed. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/architecture/cloud-adoption/appendix/azure-scaffoldCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "original_number": "57",
      "question": "Your company has an on-premises network that contains multiple servers.The company plans to reduce the following administrative responsibilities:✑ Backing up application data✑ Replacing failed server hardware✑ Managing physical server security✑ Updating server operating systems✑ Managing permissions to shared documentsThe company plans to migrate servers to Azure virtual machines.You need to identify which administrative responsibilities will be eliminated after the planned migration.Which two responsibilities should you identify? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.NOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Replacing failed server hardware"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Backing up application data"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Managing physical server security"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Updating server operating systems"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "Managing permissions to shared documents"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "original_number": "59",
      "question": "You plan to provision Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS) resources in Azure.Which resource is an example of IaaS?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "an Azure web app"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure virtual machine"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "an Azure logic app"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Azure SQL database"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "An Azure virtual machine is an example of Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS).Azure web app, Azure logic app and Azure SQL database are all examples of Platform as a Service (Paas). | Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/overview/what-is-iaas/https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/overview/what-is-paas"
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "original_number": "60",
      "question": "To which cloud models can you deploy physical servers?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "private cloud and hybrid cloud only"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "private cloud only"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "private cloud, hybrid cloud and public cloud"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "hybrid cloud only"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "A private cloud is on-premises so you can deploy physical servers.A hybrid cloud is a mix of on-premise and public cloud resources. You can deploy physical servers on-premises. | Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/overview/what-is-hybrid-cloud-computing"
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "original_number": "63",
      "question": "You have 50 virtual machines hosted on-premises and 50 virtual machines hosted in Azure. The on-premises virtual machines and the Azurevirtual machines connect to each other.Which type of cloud model is this?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "hybrid"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "private"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "public"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/overview/what-is-hybrid-cloud-computing"
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "original_number": "65",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.Your company plans to migrate all its data and resources to Azure.The company's migration plan states that only Platform as a Service (PaaS) solutions must be used in Azure.You need to deploy an Azure environment that meets the company migration plan.Solution: You create Azure virtual machines, Azure SQL databases, and Azure Storage accounts.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Platform as a service (PaaS) is a complete development and deployment environment in the cloud. PaaS includes infrastructure ג \"€servers,storage, and networking ג \"€but also middleware, development tools, business intelligence (BI) services, database management systems, andmore. PaaS is designed to support the complete web application lifecycle: building, testing, deploying, managing, and updating.However, virtual machines are examples of Infrastructure as a service (IaaS). IaaS is an instant computing infrastructure, provisioned andmanaged over the internet. | Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-paas/https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-iaas"
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "original_number": "66",
      "question": "Your company plans to deploy several custom applications to Azure. The applications will provide invoicing services to the customers of thecompany. Each application will have several prerequisite applications and services installed.You need to recommend a cloud deployment solution for all the applications.What should you recommend?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Software as a Service (SaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Platform as a Service (PaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Infrastructure as a Service (laaS)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-iaas/https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-saas/https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-paas"
    },
    {
      "id": 49,
      "original_number": "73",
      "question": "Your company plans to migrate all its data and resources to Azure.The company's migration plan states that only Platform as a Service (PaaS) solutions must be used in Azure.You need to deploy an Azure environment that meets the company's migration plan.What should you create?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure virtual machines, Azure SQL databases, and Azure Storage accounts."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure App Service and Azure virtual machines that have Microsoft SQL Server installed."
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "an Azure App Service and Azure SQL databases."
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure storage accounts and web server in Azure virtual machines."
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Azure App Service and Azure SQL databases are examples of Azure PaaS solutions. Therefore, this solution does meet the goal."
    },
    {
      "id": 50,
      "original_number": "74",
      "question": "What does a customer provide in a software as a service (SaaS) model?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "application data"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "data storage"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "compute resources"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "application software"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "SaaS provides a complete software solution which you purchase on a pay-as-you-go basis from a cloud service provider. You rent the use of anapp for your organization and your users connect to it over the Internet, usually with a web browser. All of the underlying infrastructure,middleware, app software and app data are located in the service provider's data center. The service provider manages the hardware andsoftware and with the appropriate service agreement, will ensure the availability and the security of the app and your data as well. | Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-in/overview/what-is-saas"
    },
    {
      "id": 51,
      "original_number": "77",
      "question": "What is the +rst stage in the Microsoft Cloud Adoption Framework for Azure?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Adopt the cloud."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Make a plan."
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Ready your organization."
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "De+ne your strategy."
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cloud-adoption-framework/overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 52,
      "original_number": "83",
      "question": "You have an accounting application named App1 that uses a legacy database.You plan to move App1 to the cloud.Which service model should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "platform as a service (PaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "infrastructure as a service (IaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "software as a service (SaaS)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Cloud Infrastructure-based Applications ג \"€It moves your existing on-premises apps to the Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS) platform or re-hosts them. ג€Lift & Shiftג €is a common term for this type of relocation. The programs will be nearly identical to what they were before, butthey will now be able to run on cloud VMs. | Reference: https://techtaalk.com/microsoft-azure-for-legacy-application-modernization"
    },
    {
      "id": 53,
      "original_number": "87",
      "question": "Which cloud computing model includes on-premises and cloud-based resources?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "hybrid"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "public"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "private"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "A hybrid cloud ג \"€sometimes called a cloud hybrid ג \"€is a computing environment that combines an on-premises datacenter (also called aprivate cloud) with a public cloud, allowing data and applications to be shared between them. Some people de+ne hybrid cloud to includeג€multicloudג €con+gurations where an organization uses more than one public cloud in addition to their on-premises datacenter. | Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-hybrid-cloud-computing"
    },
    {
      "id": 54,
      "original_number": "90",
      "question": "Which term represents the ability to increase the computing capacity of a virtual machine by adding memory or CPUs?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "agility"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "vertical scaling"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "horizontal scaling"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "elasticity"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Vertical scaling, also known as scale up and scale down, means increasing or decreasing virtual machine (VM) sizes in response to a workload.Compare this behavior with horizontal scaling, also referred to as scale out and scale in, where the number of VMs is altered depending on theworkload. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machine-scale-sets/virtual-machine-scale-sets-vertical-scale-reprovisionCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 55,
      "original_number": "91",
      "question": "What are two bene+ts of cloud computing? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.NOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "enables the rapid provisioning of resources"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "has increased administrative complexity"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "has the same con+guration options as on-premises"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "shifts capital expenditures (CAPEX) to operating expenditures (OPEX)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://www.protechtraining.com/blog/post/top-5-bene+ts-of-microsoft-azure-for-business-934"
    },
    {
      "id": 56,
      "original_number": "92",
      "question": "What is a feature of an Azure virtual network?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "resource cost analysis"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "packet inspection"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "geo-redundancy"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "isolation and segmentation"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "Implement network segmentation patterns on Azure.A uni+ed enterprise segmentation strategy guides technical teams to consistently segment access using networking, applications, identity, andany other access controls. Create segmentation in your network footprint by de+ning perimeters.The main reasons for segmentation are:The ability to group related assets that are a part of (or support) workload operations.Isolation of resources.Governance policies set by the organization. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/architecture/framework/security/design-network-segmentationCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 57,
      "original_number": "95",
      "question": "Which cloud computing bene+t provides continuous user access to a cloud-based application with minimal downtime?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "agility"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "scalability"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "elasticity"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "high availability"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 58,
      "original_number": "96",
      "question": "You need to identify the type of failure for which an Azure Availability Zone can be used to protect access to Azure services.What should you identify?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a physical server failure"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure region failure"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a storage failure"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Azure data center failure"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "Availability zones expand the level of control you have to maintain the availability of the applications and data on your VMs. An Availability Zoneis a physically separate zone, within an Azure region. There are three Availability Zones per supported Azure region.Each Availability Zone has a distinct power source, network, and cooling. By architecting your solutions to use replicated VMs in zones, you canprotect your apps and data from the loss of a datacenter. If one zone is compromised, then replicated apps and data are instantly available inanother zone. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machines/availabilityCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 59,
      "original_number": "98",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.You plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.You need to ensure that the services running on the virtual machines are available if a single data center fails.Solution: You deploy the virtual machines to two or more resource groups.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "A resource group is a logical container for Azure resources. When you create a resource group, you specify which location to create theresource group in.However, when you create a virtual machine and place it in the resource group, the virtual machine can still be in a different location (differentdatacenter).Therefore, creating multiple resource groups, even if they are in separate datacenters does not ensure that the services running on the virtualmachines are available if a single data center fails. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-resource-manager/management/overview#resource-groupsCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 60,
      "original_number": "99",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.You plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.You need to ensure that the services running on the virtual machines are available if a single data center fails.Solution: You deploy the virtual machines to a scale set.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "This answer does not specify that the scale set will be con+gured across multiple data centers so this solution does not meet the goal.Azure virtual machine scale sets let you create and manage a group of load balanced VMs. The number of VM instances can automaticallyincrease or decrease in response to demand or a de+ned schedule. Scale sets provide high availability to your applications, and allow you tocentrally manage, con+gure, and update many VMs.Virtual machines in a scale set can be deployed across multiple update domains and fault domains to maximize availability and resilience tooutages due to data center outages, and planned or unplanned maintenance events. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machine-scale-sets/availabilityCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 61,
      "original_number": "101",
      "question": "This question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.Resource groups provide organizations with the ability to manage the compliance of Azure resources across multiple subscriptions.Instructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select theanswer choice that makes the statement correct.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "No change is needed"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Management groups"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure policies"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure App Service plans"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/governance/policy/overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 62,
      "original_number": "102",
      "question": "Your company plans to migrate to Azure.The company has several departments. All the Azure resources used by each department will be managed by a department administrator.What are two possible techniques to segment Azure for the departments? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.NOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "multiple subscriptions"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "multiple Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) directories"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "multiple regions"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "multiple resource groups"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "DAn Azure subscription is a container for Azure resources. It is also a boundary for permissions to resources and for billing. You are chargedmonthly for all resources in a subscription. A single Azure tenant (Azure Active Directory) can contain multiple Azure subscriptions.A resource group is a container that holds related resources for an Azure solution. The resource group can include all the resources for thesolution, or only those resources that you want to manage as a group.To enable each department administrator to manage the Azure resources used by that department, you will need to create a separatesubscription per department. You can then assign each department administrator as an administrator for the subscription to enable them tomanage all resources in that subscription. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cost-management-billing/manage/create-subscription"
    },
    {
      "id": 63,
      "original_number": "105",
      "question": "You have an Azure environment that contains multiple Azure virtual machines.You plan to implement a solution that enables the client computers on your on-premises network to communicate to the Azure virtual machines.You need to recommend which Azure resources must be created for the planned solution.Which two Azure resources should you include in the recommendation? Each correct answer presents part of the solution.NOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a virtual network gateway"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a load balancer"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "an application gateway"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a virtual network"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "a gateway subnet"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "ETo implement a solution that enables the client computers on your on-premises network to communicate to the Azure virtual machines, youneed to con+gure aVPN (Virtual Private Network) to connect the on-premises network to the Azure virtual network.The Azure VPN device is known as a Virtual Network Gateway. The virtual network gateway needs to be located in a dedicated subnet in theAzure virtual network. This dedicated subnet is known as a gateway subnet and must be named 'GatewaySubnet'.Note: a virtual network (answer D) is also required. However, as we already have virtual machines deployed in a Azure, we can assume that thevirtual network is already in place. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/ohce365/enterprise/connect-an-on-premises-network-to-a-microsoft-azure-virtual-networkCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 64,
      "original_number": "106",
      "question": "You attempt to create several managed Microsoft SQL Server instances in an Azure environment and receive a message that you must increaseyour Azure subscription limits.What should you do to increase the limits?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Create a service health alert"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Upgrade your support plan"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Modify an Azure policy"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Create a new support request"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "Many Azure resource have quote limits. The purpose of the quota limits is to help you control your Azure costs. However, it is common torequire an increase to the default quota.You can request a quota limit increase by opening a support request. In the support request, select 'Service and subscription limits (quotas)' forthe Issue type, select your subscription and the service you want to increase the quota for. For this question, you would select 'SQL DatabaseManaged Instance' as the quote type. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/sql-database/sql-database-managed-instance-resource-limits#obtaining-a-larger-quota-for-sql-managed-instanceCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 65,
      "original_number": "110",
      "question": "Your company plans to move several servers to Azure.The company's compliance policy states that a server named FinServer must be on a separate network segment.You are evaluating which Azure services can be used to meet the compliance policy requirements.Which Azure solution should you recommend?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a resource group for FinServer and another resource group for all the other servers"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a virtual network for FinServer and another virtual network for all the other servers"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a VPN for FinServer and a virtual network gateway for each other server"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "one resource group for all the servers and a resource lock for FinServer"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Networks in Azure are known as virtual networks. A virtual network can have multiple IP address spaces and multiple subnets. Azureautomatically routes trahc between different subnets within a virtual network.The question states that FinServer must be on a separate network segment. The only way to separate FinServer from the other servers innetworking terms is to place the server in a different virtual network to the other servers. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-network/virtual-network-vnet-plan-design-armCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 66,
      "original_number": "111",
      "question": "You plan to map a network drive from several computers that run Windows 10 to Azure Storage.You need to create a storage solution in Azure for the planned mapped drive.What should you create?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "an Azure SQL database"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a virtual machine data disk"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a File service in a storage account"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a Blob service in a storage account"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/storage/+les/storage-how-to-use-+les-windowsCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 67,
      "original_number": "113",
      "question": "Your company plans to start using Azure and will migrate all its network resources to Azure.You need to start the planning process by exploring Azure.What should you create +rst?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a subscription"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a resource group"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a virtual network"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a management group"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/ohce365/enterprise/subscriptions-licenses-accounts-and-tenants-for-microsoft-cloud-offeringsCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 68,
      "original_number": "117",
      "question": "Which Azure service should you use to collect events from multiple resources into a centralized repository?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Event Hubs"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Analysis Services"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Monitor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Stream Analytics"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Azure Event Hubs is a big data streaming platform and event ingestion service. It can receive and process millions of events per second. Datasent to an event hub can be transformed and stored by using any real-time analytics provider or batching/storage adapters.Azure Event Hubs can be used to ingest, buffer, store, and process your stream in real time to get actionable insights. Event Hubs uses apartitioned consumer model, enabling multiple applications to process the stream concurrently and letting you control the speed of processing.Azure Event Hubs can be used to capture your data in near-real time in an Azure Blob storage or Azure Data Lake Storageג€‰for long-termretention or micro-batch processing. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/event-hubs/event-hubs-aboutCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 69,
      "original_number": "122",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.You plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.You need to ensure that the services running on the virtual machines are available if a single data center fails.Solution: You deploy the virtual machines to two or more scale sets.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "This answer does not specify that the scale set will be con+gured across multiple data centers so this solution does not meet the goal.Azure virtual machine scale sets let you create and manage a group of load balanced VMs. The number of VM instances can automaticallyincrease or decrease in response to demand or a de+ned schedule. Scale sets provide high availability to your applications, and allow you tocentrally manage, con+gure, and update many VMs.Virtual machines in a scale set can be deployed across multiple update domains and fault domains to maximize availability and resilience tooutages due to data center outages, and planned or unplanned maintenance events. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machine-scale-sets/availabilityCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 70,
      "original_number": "123",
      "question": "You need to be noti+ed when Microsoft plans to perform maintenance that can affect the resources deployed to an Azure subscription.What should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Monitor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Service Health"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Microsoft Trust Center"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Azure Service Health provides a personalized view of the health of the Azure services and regions you're using. This is the best place to look forservice impacting communications about outages, planned maintenance activities, and other health advisories because the authenticatedService Health experience knows which services and resources you currently use. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/service-health/overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 71,
      "original_number": "131",
      "question": "You plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.You need to ensure that the services running on the virtual machines remain available if a single data center fails.What are two possible solutions? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Deploy the virtual machines to two or more availability zones."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Deploy the virtual machines to two or more resource groups."
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Deploy the virtual machines to a scale set."
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Deploy the virtual machines to two or more regions."
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machine-scale-sets/overview"
    },
    {
      "id": 72,
      "original_number": "135",
      "question": "What is the most severe failure from which an Azure Availability Zone can be used to protect access to Azure service?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a physical server failure"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure region failure"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a storage failure"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Azure data center failure"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "Availability zones expand the level of control you have to maintain the availability of the applications and data on your VMs. An Availability Zoneis a physically separate zone, within an Azure region. There are three Availability Zones per supported Azure region.Each Availability Zone has a distinct power source, network, and cooling. By architecting your solutions to use replicated VMs in zones, you canprotect your apps and data from the loss of a datacenter. If one zone is compromised, then replicated apps and data are instantly available inanother zone. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machines/availabilityCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 73,
      "original_number": "136",
      "question": "You need to purchase a third-party virtual security appliance that you will deploy to an Azure subscription.What should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure subscriptions"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Security Center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Marketplace"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Microsoft Store"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cost-management-billing/manage/ea-azure-marketplaceCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 74,
      "original_number": "142",
      "question": "You need to purchase a third-party virtual security appliance that you will deploy to an Azure subscription.What should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure subscriptions"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Microsoft Defender for Cloud"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Marketplace"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Microsoft Store"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "You can access these enhanced network security features by using an Azure partner solution. You can +nd the most current Azure partnernetwork security solutions by visiting the Azure Marketplace, and searching for \"security\" and \"network security.\"Some third-party reseller services available on Azure Marketplace now consume your Enterprise Agreement (EA) Azure Prepayment balance. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/security/fundamentals/network-overview"
    },
    {
      "id": 75,
      "original_number": "144",
      "question": "You plan to deploy a service to Azure virtual machines.You need to ensure that the service will be available if a datacenter fails.What should you use as part of the virtual machine deployment?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "availability sets"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "proximity placement groups"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "host groups"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "availability zones"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "Azure availability zones are physically separate locations within each Azure region that are tolerant to local failures. Failures can range fromsoftware and hardware failures to events such as earthquakes, joods, and +res. Tolerance to failures is achieved because of redundancy andlogical isolation of Azure services. To ensure resiliency, a minimum of three separate availability zones are present in all availability zone-enabled regions. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/availability-zones/az-overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 76,
      "original_number": "145",
      "question": "Your company has an Azure subscription that contains resources in several regions.You need to ensure that administrators can only create resources in those regions.What should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a read-only lock"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure policy"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a management group"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a reservation"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 77,
      "original_number": "148",
      "question": "What is the function of a Site-to-Site VPN?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "provides a secure connection between a computer on a public network and the corporate network"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "provides a dedicated private connection to Azure that does NOT travel over the internet"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "provides a connection from an on-premises VPN device to an Azure VPN gateway"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "A Site-to-Site VPN gateway connection is used to connect your on-premises network to an Azure virtual network over an IPsec/IKE (IKEv1 orIKEv2) VPN tunnel.This type of connection requires a VPN device located on-premises that has an externally facing public IP address assigned to it.Example: | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/vpn-gateway/vpn-gateway-howto-site-to-site-classic-portalCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 78,
      "original_number": "151",
      "question": "You need to manage containers.Which two services can you use? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.NOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Virtual Desktop"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure virtual machines"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Functions"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Container Instances"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "ERun Docker containers on-demand in a managed, serverless Azure environment. Azure Container Instances is a solution for any scenario thatcan operate in isolated containers, without orchestration. Run event-driven applications, quickly deploy from your container developmentpipelines, and run data processing and build jobs.You can manage containers at scale with a fully managed Kubernetes container management and orchestration service that integrates withAzure ActiveDirectory.Azure Kubernetes Service is a robust and cost-effective container orchestration service that helps you to deploy and manage containerizedapplications in seconds where additional resources are assigned automatically without the headache of managing additional servers. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/container-instances/https://cloudacademy.com/blog/azure-kubernetes-service-aks-what-is-it-and-why-do-we-use-itCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 79,
      "original_number": "153",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.You plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.You need to ensure that the services running on the virtual machines are available if a single data center fails.Solution: You deploy the virtual machines to two or more availability zones.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Availability zones expand the level of control you have to maintain the availability of the applications and data on your VMs. An Availability Zoneis a physically separate zone, within an Azure region. There are three Availability Zones per supported Azure region.Each Availability Zone has a distinct power source, network, and cooling. By architecting your solutions to use replicated VMs in zones, you canprotect your apps and data from the loss of a datacenter. If one zone is compromised, then replicated apps and data are instantly available inanother zone. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machine-scale-sets/availabilityCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 80,
      "original_number": "154",
      "question": "This question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.One of the bene+ts of Azure SQL Data Warehouse is that high availability is built into the platform.Instructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select theanswer choice that makes the statement correct.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "No change is needed"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "automatic scaling"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "data compression"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "versioning"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Azure Data Warehouse (now known as Azure Synapse Analytics) is a PaaS offering from Microsoft. As with all PaaS services from Microsoft,SQL DataWarehouse offers an availability SLA of 99.9%. Microsoft can offer 99.9% availability because it has high availability features built into theplatform. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/sql-data-warehouse/sql-data-warehouse-overview-faqCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 81,
      "original_number": "155",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.You plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.You need to ensure that the services running on the virtual machines are available if a single data center fails.Solution: You deploy the virtual machines to two or more regions.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "By deploying the virtual machines to two or more regions, you are deploying the virtual machines to multiple datacenters. This will ensure thatthe services running on the virtual machines are available if a single data center fails.Azure operates in multiple datacenters around the world. These datacenters are grouped in to geographic regions, giving you jexibility inchoosing where to build your applications.You create Azure resources in de+ned geographic regions like 'West US', 'North Europe', or 'Southeast Asia'. You can review the list of regionsand their locations.Within each region, multiple datacenters exist to provide for redundancy and availability. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machines/windows/regionsCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 82,
      "original_number": "157",
      "question": "At which OSI layer does ExpressRoute operate?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Layer 2"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Layer 3"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Layer 5"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Layer 7"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "ExpressRoute circuit. A layer 2 or layer 3 circuit supplied by the connectivity provider that joins the on-premises network with Azure through theedge routers. The circuit uses the hardware infrastructure managed by the connectivity provider.In OSI terms, you start from layer 2ג€¦ The ג€Network Service Providerג €concept was a managed concept, where you got a layer 3 solution (inOSI terms). The telecom provider took care of all the complexity for you. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/architecture/reference-architectures/hybrid-networking/expressrouteCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 83,
      "original_number": "160",
      "question": "You plan to store 20 TB of data in Azure. The data will be accessed infrequently and visualized by using Microsoft Power BI.You need to recommend a storage solution for the data.Which two solutions should you recommend? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.NOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Data Lake"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Cosmos DB"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure SQL Data Warehouse"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure SQL Database"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "Azure Database for PostgreSQL"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "CYou can use Power BI to analyze and visualize data stored in Azure Data Lake and Azure SQL Data Warehouse.Azure Data Lake includes all of the capabilities required to make it easy for developers, data scientists and analysts to store data of any sizeand shape and at any speed, and do all types of processing and analytics across platforms and languages. It removes the complexities ofingesting and storing all your data while making it faster to get up and running with batch, streaming and interactive analytics. It also integratesseamlessly with operational stores and data warehouses so that you can extend current data applications. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/data-lake-store/data-lake-store-power-bi"
    },
    {
      "id": 84,
      "original_number": "164",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.An Azure administrator plans to run a PowerShell script that creates Azure resources.You need to recommend which computer con+guration to use to run the script.Solution: Run the script from a computer that runs Linux and has the Azure CLI tools installed.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "A PowerShell script is a +le that contains PowerShell cmdlets and code. A PowerShell script needs to be run in PowerShell.PowerShell can now be installed on Linux. However, the question states that the computer has Azure CLI tools, not PowerShell installed.Therefore, this solution does not meet the goal. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/powershell/scripting/components/ise/how-to-write-and-run-scripts-in-the-windows-powershell-ise?view=powershell-6Community"
    },
    {
      "id": 85,
      "original_number": "165",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.An Azure administrator plans to run a PowerShell script that creates Azure resources.You need to recommend which computer con+guration to use to run the script.Solution: Run the script from a computer that runs Chrome OS and uses Azure Cloud Shell.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "A PowerShell script is a +le that contains PowerShell cmdlets and code. A PowerShell script needs to be run in PowerShell.With the Azure Cloud Shell, you can run PowerShell cmdlets and scripts in a Web browser. You log in to the Azure Portal and select the AzureCloud Shell option.This will open a PowerShell session in the Web browser. The Azure Cloud Shell has the necessary Azure PowerShell module installed.Note: to run a PowerShell script in the Azure Cloud Shell, you need to change to the directory where the PowerShell script is stored. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cloud-shell/quickstart-powershellCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 86,
      "original_number": "167",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.An Azure administrator plans to run a PowerShell script that creates Azure resources.You need to recommend which computer con+guration to use to run the script.Solution: Run the script from a computer that runs macOS and has PowerShell Core 6.0 installed.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "A PowerShell script is a +le that contains PowerShell cmdlets and code. A PowerShell script needs to be run in PowerShell.In this question, the computer has PowerShell Core 6.0 installed. Therefore, this solution does meet the goal.Note: To create Azure resources using PowerShell, you would need to import the Azure PowerShell module which includes the PowerShellcmdlets required to create the resources. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/powershell/scripting/components/ise/how-to-write-and-run-scripts-in-the-windows-powershell-ise?view=powershell-6Community"
    },
    {
      "id": 87,
      "original_number": "172",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.You have an Azure environment. You need to create a new Azure virtual machine from a tablet that runs the Android operating system.Solution: You use Bash in Azure Cloud Shell.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "With Azure Cloud Shell, you can create virtual machines using Bash or PowerShell.Azure Cloud Shell is an interactive, authenticated, browser-accessible shell for managing Azure resources. It provides the jexibility of choosingthe shell experience that best suits the way you work, either Bash or PowerShell. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cloud-shell/quickstart"
    },
    {
      "id": 88,
      "original_number": "173",
      "question": "You have an on-premises application that sends email noti+cations automatically based on a rule.You plan to migrate the application to Azure.You need to recommend a serverless computing solution for the application.What should you include in the recommendation?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a web app"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a server image in Azure Marketplace"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a logic app"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an API app"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/logic-apps/logic-apps-overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 89,
      "original_number": "174",
      "question": "You plan to deploy a website to Azure. The website will be accessed by users worldwide and will host large video +les.You need to recommend which Azure feature must be used to provide the best video playback experience.What should you recommend?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "an application gateway"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure ExpressRoute circuit"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a content delivery network (CDN)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Azure Trahc Manager pro+le"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cdn/cdn-overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 90,
      "original_number": "175",
      "question": "Your company plans to deploy several million sensors that will upload data to Azure.You need to identify which Azure resources must be created to support the planned solution.Which two Azure resources should you identify? Each correct answer presents part of the solution.NOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Data Lake"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Queue storage"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure File Storage"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure IoT Hub"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "Azure Noti+cation Hubs"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "DIoT Hub (Internet of things Hub) provides data from millions of sensors.IoT Hub is a managed service, hosted in the cloud, that acts as a central message hub for bi-directional communication between your IoTapplication and the devices it manages. You can use Azure IoT Hub to build IoT solutions with reliable and secure communications betweenmillions of IoT devices and a cloud- hosted solution backend. You can connect virtually any device to IoT Hub.There are two storage services IoT Hub can route messages to -- Azure Blob Storage and Azure Data Lake Storage Gen2 (ADLS Gen2) accounts.Azure DataLake Storage accounts are hierarchical namespace-enabled storage accounts built on top of blob storage. Both of these use blobs for theirstorage. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/iot-hub/about-iot-hubhttps://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/iot-hub/iot-hub-devguide-messages-d2cCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 91,
      "original_number": "176",
      "question": "You have an Azure web app.You need to manage the settings of the web app from an iPhone.What are two Azure management tools that you can use? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.NOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure CLI"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "the Azure portal"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Cloud Shell"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Windows PowerShell"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "Azure Storage Explorer"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "CThe Azure portal is the web-based portal for managing Azure. Being web-based, you can use the Azure portal on an iPhone.Azure Cloud Shell is a web-based command line for managing Azure. You access the Azure Cloud Shell from the Azure portal. Being web-based,you can use theAzure Cloud Shell on an iPhone.Incorrect Answers:A: Azure CLI can be installed on MacOS but it cannot be installed on an iPhone.D: Windows PowerShell can be installed on MacOS but it cannot be installed on an iPhone.E: Azure Storage Explorer is not used to manage Azure web apps. | Reference: http://www.deployazure.com/management/managing-azure-from-ipad"
    },
    {
      "id": 92,
      "original_number": "177",
      "question": "Your company plans to deploy an Arti+cial Intelligence (AI) solution in Azure.What should the company use to build, test, and deploy predictive analytics solutions?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Logic Apps"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Machine Learning Designer"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Batch"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Cosmos DB"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Azure Machine Learning designer lets you visually connect datasets and modules on an interactive canvas to create machine learning models. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/machine-learning/concept-designerCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 93,
      "original_number": "179",
      "question": "What can you use to automatically send an alert if an administrator stops an Azure virtual machine?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Service Health"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Monitor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Network Watcher"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-monitor/insights/vminsights-alertsCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 94,
      "original_number": "181",
      "question": "You have an Azure environment.You need to create a new Azure virtual machine from a tablet that runs the Android operating system.What are three possible solutions? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.NOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Use Bash in Azure Cloud Shell."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Use PowerShell in Azure Cloud Shell."
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Use the PowerApps portal."
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Use the Security & Compliance admin center."
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "Use the Azure portal."
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "BEThe Android tablet device will have a web browser (Chrome). That's enough to connect to the Azure portal.The Azure portal offers three ways to create a VM:✑ Using the graphical portal.✑ Using the Azure Cloud Shell using Bash.✑ Using the Azure Cloud Shell using PowerShell."
    },
    {
      "id": 95,
      "original_number": "182",
      "question": "A team of developers at your company plans to deploy, and then remove, 50 virtual machines each week. All the virtual machines are con+guredby using AzureResource Manager templates.You need to recommend which Azure service will minimize the administrative effort required to deploy and remove the virtual machines.What should you recommend?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Reserved Virtual Machine (VM) Instances"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure DevTest Labs"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure virtual machine scale sets"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Virtual Desktop"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "DevTest Labs creates labs consisting of pre-con+gured bases or Azure Resource Manager templates.By using DevTest Labs, you can test the latest versions of your applications by doing the following tasks:✑ Quickly provision Windows and Linux environments by using reusable templates and artifacts.✑ Easily integrate your deployment pipeline with DevTest Labs to provision on-demand environments.✑ Scale up your load testing by provisioning multiple test agents and create pre-provisioned environments for training and demos. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/lab-services/devtest-lab-overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 96,
      "original_number": "184",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.You have an Azure subscription named Subscription1. You sign in to the Azure portal and create a resource group named RG1.From Azure documentation, you have the following command that creates a virtual machine named VM1. az vm create --resource-group RG1 --name VM1 --image UbuntuL TS --generate-ssh-keysYou need to create VM1 in Subscription1 by using the command.Solution: From the Azure portal, launch Azure Cloud Shell and select PowerShell. Run the command in Cloud Shell.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "The command can be run in the Azure Cloud Shell. Although this question says you select PowerShell rather than Bash, the Az commands willwork inPowerShell.The Azure Cloud Shell is a free interactive shell. It has common Azure tools preinstalled and con+gured to use with your account.To open the Cloud Shell, just select Try it from the upper right corner of a code block. You can also launch Cloud Shell in a separate browser tabby going to https://shell.azure.com/bash. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machines/linux/quick-create-cliCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 97,
      "original_number": "185",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.You have an Azure subscription named Subscription1. You sign in to the Azure portal and create a resource group named RG1.From Azure documentation, you have the following command that creates a virtual machine named VM1. az vm create --resource-group RG1 --name VM1 --image UbuntuL TS--generate-ssh-keysYou need to create VM1 in Subscription1 by using the command.Solution: From a computer that runs Windows 10, install Azure CLI. From PowerShell, sign in to Azure and then run the command.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "The command can be run from PowerShell or the command prompt if you have the Azure CLI installed. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/cli/azure/install-azure-cli-windows?view=azure-cli-latestCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 98,
      "original_number": "186",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.You have an Azure subscription named Subscription1. You sign in to the Azure portal and create a resource group named RG1.From Azure documentation, you have the following command that creates a virtual machine named VM1. az vm create --resource-group RG1 --name VM1 --image UbuntuL TS--generate-ssh-keysYou need to create VM1 in Subscription1 by using the command.Solution: From a computer that runs Windows 10, install Azure CLI. From a command prompt, sign in to Azure and then run the command.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "The command can be run from PowerShell or the command prompt if you have the Azure CLI installed. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/cli/azure/install-azure-cli-windows?view=azure-cli-latestCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 99,
      "original_number": "191",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.An Azure administrator plans to run a PowerShell script that creates Azure resources.You need to recommend which computer con+guration to use to run the script.Solution: Run the script from a computer that runs Windows 10 and has the Azure PowerShell module installed.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "A PowerShell script is a +le that contains PowerShell cmdlets and code. A PowerShell script needs to be run in PowerShell.In this question, the computer has the Azure PowerShell module installed. Therefore, this solution does meet the goal. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/powershell/scripting/components/ise/how-to-write-and-run-scripts-in-the-windows-powershell-ise?view=powershell-6Community"
    },
    {
      "id": 100,
      "original_number": "193",
      "question": "Which service provides serverless computing in Azure?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Virtual Machines"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Functions"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure storage account"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure dedicated hosts"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Azure Functions provide a platform for serverless code.Azure Functions is a serverless compute service that lets you run event-triggered code without having to explicitly provision or manageinfrastructure. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-functions"
    },
    {
      "id": 101,
      "original_number": "194",
      "question": "An Azure administrator plans to run a PowerShell script that creates Azure resources.You need to recommend which computer con+guration to use to run the script.Which three computers can run the script? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.NOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a computer that runs macOS and has PowerShell Core 6.0 installed."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a computer that runs Windows 10 and has the Azure PowerShell module installed."
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a computer that runs Linux and has the Azure PowerShell module installed."
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a computer that runs Linux and has the Azure CLI tools installed."
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "a computer that runs Chrome OS and uses Azure Cloud Shell."
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "BEA PowerShell script is a +le that contains PowerShell cmdlets and code. A PowerShell script needs to be run in PowerShell. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/powershell/scripting/components/ise/how-to-write-and-run-scripts-in-the-windows-powershell-ise?view=powershell-6"
    },
    {
      "id": 102,
      "original_number": "195",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.You have an Azure subscription named Subscription1. You sign in to the Azure portal and create a resource group named RG1.From Azure documentation, you have the following command that creates a virtual machine named VM1. az vm create --resource-group RG1 --name VM1 --image UbuntuL TS --generate-ssh-keysYou need to create VM1 in Subscription1 by using the command.Solution: From the Azure portal, launch Azure Cloud Shell and select Bash. Run the command in Cloud Shell.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "The command can be run in the Azure Cloud Shell.The Azure Cloud Shell is a free interactive shell. It has common Azure tools preinstalled and con+gured to use with your account.To open the Cloud Shell, just select Try it from the upper right corner of a code block. You can also launch Cloud Shell in a separate browser tabby going to https://shell.azure.com/bash. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machines/linux/quick-create-cliCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 103,
      "original_number": "196",
      "question": "Your company has several business units.Each business unit requires 20 different Azure resources for daily operation. All the business units require the same type of Azure resources.You need to recommend a solution to automate the creation of the Azure resources.What should you include in the recommendations?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Resource Manager templates"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "virtual machine scale sets"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "the Azure API Management service"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "management groups"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "You can use Azure Resource Manager templates to automate the creation of the Azure resources. Deploying resource through templates isknown as'Infrastructure as code'.To implement infrastructure as code for your Azure solutions, use Azure Resource Manager templates. The template is a JavaScript ObjectNotation (JSON) +le that de+nes the infrastructure and con+guration for your project. The template uses declarative syntax, which lets youstate what you intend to deploy without having to write the sequence of programming commands to create it. In the template, you specify theresources to deploy and the properties for those resources. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-resource-manager/templates/overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 104,
      "original_number": "198",
      "question": "What can you use to identify underutilized or unused Azure virtual machines?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Cost Management + Billing"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure reservations"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Policy"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Azure Advisor helps you optimize and reduce your overall Azure spend by identifying idle and underutilized resources. You can get costrecommendations from the Cost tab on the Advisor dashboard. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/advisor/advisor-overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 105,
      "original_number": "203",
      "question": "A team of developers at your company plans to deploy, and then remove, 50 customized virtual machines each week. Thirty of the virtualmachines run WindowsServer 2016 and 20 of the virtual machines run Ubuntu Linux.You need to recommend which Azure service will minimize the administrative effort required to deploy and remove the virtual machines.What should you recommend?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Reserved Virtual Machines (VM) Instances"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure virtual machine scale sets"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure DevTest Labs"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Microsoft Managed Desktop"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "DevTest Labs creates labs consisting of pre-con+gured bases or Azure Resource Manager templates.By using DevTest Labs, you can test the latest versions of your applications by doing the following tasks:✑ Quickly provision Windows and Linux environments by using reusable templates and artifacts.✑ Easily integrate your deployment pipeline with DevTest Labs to provision on-demand environments.✑ Scale up your load testing by provisioning multiple test agents and create pre-provisioned environments for training and demos. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/lab-services/devtest-lab-overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 106,
      "original_number": "205",
      "question": "A support engineer plans to perform several Azure management tasks by using the Azure CLI.You install the CLI on a computer.You need to tell the support engineer which tools to use to run the CLI.Which two tools should you instruct the support engineer to use? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.NOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Command Prompt"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Resource Explorer"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Windows PowerShell"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Windows Defender Firewall"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "Network and Sharing Center"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "CFor Windows the Azure CLI is installed via an MSI, which gives you access to the CLI through the Windows Command Prompt (CMD) orPowerShell. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/cli/azure/install-azure-cli-windows?view=azure-cli-latestCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 107,
      "original_number": "206",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.You have an Azure environment. You need to create a new Azure virtual machine from a tablet that runs the Android operating system.Solution: You use PowerShell in Azure Cloud Shell.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Azure Cloud Shell is a browser-based shell experience to manage and develop Azure resources.Cloud Shell offers a browser-accessible, pre-con+gured shell experience for managing Azure resources without the overhead of installing,versioning, and maintaining a machine yourself.Being browser-based, Azure Cloud Shell can be run on a browser from a tablet that runs the Android operating system. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cloud-shell/featuresCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 108,
      "original_number": "207",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.You have an Azure environment. You need to create a new Azure virtual machine from a tablet that runs the Android operating system.Solution: You use the PowerApps portal.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "PowerApps lets you quickly build business applications with little or no code. It is not used to create Azure virtual machines. Therefore, thissolution does not meet the goal.PowerApps Portals allow organizations to create websites which can be shared with users external to their organization either anonymously orthrough the login provider of their choice like LinkedIn, Microsoft Account, other commercial login providers. | Reference: https://powerapps.microsoft.com/en-us/blog/introducing-powerapps-portals-powerful-low-code-websites-for-external-users"
    },
    {
      "id": 109,
      "original_number": "208",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.You have an Azure environment. You need to create a new Azure virtual machine from a tablet that runs the Android operating system.Solution: You use the Azure portal.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "The Azure portal is a web-based, uni+ed console that provides an alternative to command-line tools. With the Azure portal, you can manageyour Azure subscription using a graphical user interface. You can build, manage, and monitor everything from simple web apps to complexcloud deployments. Create custom dashboards for an organized view of resources. Con+gure accessibility options for an optimal experience.Being web-based, the Azure portal can be run on a browser from a tablet that runs the Android operating system. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-portal/azure-portal-overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 110,
      "original_number": "214",
      "question": "Which Azure service provides a set of version control tools to manage code?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Repos"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure DevTest Labs"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Storage"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Cosmos DB"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Azure Repos is a set of version control tools that you can use to manage your code.Incorrect Answers:B: Azure DevTest Labs creates labs consisting of pre-con+gured bases or Azure Resource Manager templates. These have all the necessarytools and software that you can use to create environments.D: Azure Cosmos DB is Microsoft's globally distributed, multi-model database service. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/devops/repos/get-started/what-is-repos?view=azure-devopsCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 111,
      "original_number": "216",
      "question": "You have a virtual machine named VM1 that runs Windows Server 2016. VM1 is in the East US Azure region.Which Azure service should you use from the Azure portal to view service failure noti+cations that can affect the availability of VM1?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Service Fabric"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Monitor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure virtual machines"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "In the Azure virtual machines page in the Azure portal, there is a named Maintenance Status. This column will display service issues that couldaffect your virtual machine. A service failure is rare but host server maintenance that could affect your virtual machines is more common.Azure periodically updates its platform to improve the reliability, performance, and security of the host infrastructure for virtual machines. Thepurpose of these updates ranges from patching software components in the hosting environment to upgrading networking components ordecommissioning hardware. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machines/maintenance-and-updatesCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 112,
      "original_number": "217",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.Your Azure environment contains multiple Azure virtual machines.You need to ensure that a virtual machine named VM1 is accessible from the Internet over HTTP .Solution: You modify an Azure Trahc Manager pro+le.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Azure Trahc Manager is a DNS-based load balancing solution. It is not used to ensure that a virtual machine named VM1 is accessible from theInternet overHTTP .To ensure that a virtual machine named VM1 is accessible from the Internet over HTTP , you need to modify a network security group or AzureFirewall.In this question, we need to add a rule to a network security group or Azure Firewall to allow the connection to the virtual machine on port 80(HTTP). | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/trahc-manager/trahc-manager-overview"
    },
    {
      "id": 113,
      "original_number": "218",
      "question": "Your company plans to deploy several web servers and several database servers to Azure.You need to recommend an Azure solution to limit the types of connections from the web servers to the database servers.What should you include in the recommendation?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "network security groups (NSGs)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Service Bus"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a local network gateway"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a route +lter"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "A network security group works like a +rewall. You can attach a network security group to a virtual network and/or individual subnets within thevirtual network.You can also attach a network security group to a network interface assigned to a virtual machine. You can use multiple network securitygroups within a virtual network to restrict trahc between resources such as virtual machines and subnets.You can +lter network trahc to and from Azure resources in an Azure virtual network with a network security group. A network security groupcontains security rules that allow or deny inbound network trahc to, or outbound network trahc from, several types of Azure resources. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-network/security-overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 114,
      "original_number": "220",
      "question": "Which service provides network trahc +ltering across multiple Azure subscriptions and virtual networks?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Firewall"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an application security group"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure DDoS protection"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a network security group (NSG)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "You can restrict trahc to multiple virtual networks in multiple subscriptions with a single Azure +rewall.Azure Firewall is a managed, cloud-based network security service that protects your Azure Virtual Network resources. It's a fully stateful+rewall as a service with built-in high availability and unrestricted cloud scalability.You can centrally create, enforce, and log application and network connectivity policies across subscriptions and virtual networks. AzureFirewall uses a static public IP address for your virtual network resources allowing outside +rewalls to identify trahc originating from yourvirtual network. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/+rewall/overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 115,
      "original_number": "221",
      "question": "Which Azure service should you use to store certi+cates?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Security Center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure Storage account"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Key Vault"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Information Protection"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Azure Key Vault is a secure store for storage various types of sensitive information including passwords and certi+cates.Azure Key Vault can be used to Securely store and tightly control access to tokens, passwords, certi+cates, API keys, and other secrets.Secrets and keys are safeguarded by Azure, using industry-standard algorithms, key lengths, and hardware security modules (HSMs). The HSMsused areFederal Information Processing Standards (FIPS) 140-2 Level 2 validated.Access to a key vault requires proper authentication and authorization before a caller (user or application) can get access. Authenticationestablishes the identity of the caller, while authorization determines the operations that they are allowed to perform. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/key-vault/key-vault-overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 116,
      "original_number": "222",
      "question": "Which Azure service can you use as a security information and event management (SIEM) solution?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Analysis Services"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Sentinel"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Information Protection"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Cognitive Services"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-in/services/azure-sentinel"
    },
    {
      "id": 117,
      "original_number": "228",
      "question": "You have an Azure virtual machine named VM1.You plan to encrypt VM1 by using Azure Disk Encryption.Which Azure resource must you create +rst?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "an Azure Storage account"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure Key Vault"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "an Azure Information Protection policy"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Encryption key"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Azure Disk Encryption requires an Azure Key Vault to control and manage disk encryption keys and secrets. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machines/windows/disk-encryption-overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 118,
      "original_number": "229",
      "question": "Which resources can be used as a source for a Network security group inbound security rule?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Service Tags only"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "IP Addresses, Service tags and Application security groups"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Application security groups only"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "IP Addresses only"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Source or destination:Any, or an individual IP address, classless inter-domain routing (CIDR) block (10.0.0.0/24, for example), service tag, or application securitygroup. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-network/network-security-groups-overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 119,
      "original_number": "233",
      "question": "You have an Azure Sentinel workspace.You need to automate responses to threats detected by Azure Sentinel.What should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "adaptive network hardening in Azure Security Center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Service Health"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Monitor workbooks"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "adaptive application controls in Azure Security Center"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 120,
      "original_number": "235",
      "question": "Which Azure service can you use as a security information and event management (SIEM) solution?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Analysis Services"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Microsoft Sentinel"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Information Protection"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Cognitive Services"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Microsoft Sentinel is a scalable, cloud-native, security information and event management (SIEM) and security orchestration, automation, andresponse (SOAR) solution. Microsoft Sentinel delivers intelligent security analytics and threat intelligence across the enterprise, providing asingle solution for attack detection, threat visibility, proactive hunting, and threat response. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/sentinel/overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 121,
      "original_number": "237",
      "question": "You have an Azure subscription.You need to review your secure score.What should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Monitor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Help + support"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Microsoft Defender for Cloud"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "The central feature in Defender for Cloud that enables you to achieve those goals is secure score. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/defender-for-cloud/secure-score-security-controlsCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 122,
      "original_number": "240",
      "question": "You need to collect and automatically analyze security events from Azure Active Directory (Azure AD).What should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Microsoft Sentinel"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Synapse Analytics"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure AD Connect"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Key Vault"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Microsoft Sentinel is a scalable, cloud-native, security information and event management (SIEM) and security orchestration, automation, andresponse (SOAR) solution.Microsoft Sentinel delivers intelligent security analytics and threat intelligence across the enterprise, providing a single solution for attackdetection, threat visibility, proactive hunting, and threat response. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/sentinel/overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 123,
      "original_number": "244",
      "question": "Your company plans to automate the deployment of servers to Azure.Your manager is concerned that you may expose administrative credentials during the deployment.You need to recommend an Azure solution that encrypts the administrative credentials during the deployment.What should you include in the recommendation?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Key Vault"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Information Protection"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Microsoft Defender for Cloud"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Azure Key Vault protects cryptographic keys, certi+cates (and the private keys associated with the certi+cates), and secrets (such asconnection strings and passwords) in the cloud. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/key-vault/general/security-featuresCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 124,
      "original_number": "248",
      "question": "You need to con+gure an Azure solution that meets the following requirements:✑ Secures websites from attacks✑ Generates reports that contain details of attempted attacksWhat should you include in the solution?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Firewall"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a network security group (NSG)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Information Protection"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "DDoS protection"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "DDoS is a type of attack that tries to exhaust application resources. The goal is to affect the application's availability and its ability to handlelegitimate requests.DDoS attacks can be targeted at any endpoint that is publicly reachable through the internet.Azure has two DDoS service offerings that provide protection from network attacks: DDoS Protection Basic and DDoS Protection Standard.DDoS Basic protection is integrated into the Azure platform by default and at no extra cost.You have the option of paying for DDoS Standard. It has several advantages over the basic service, including logging, alerting, and telemetry.DDoS Standard can generate reports that contain details of attempted attacks as required in this question. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/security/fundamentals/ddos-best-practicesCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 125,
      "original_number": "250",
      "question": "Your Azure environment contains multiple Azure virtual machines.You need to ensure that a virtual machine named VM1 is accessible from the Internet over HTTP .What are two possible solutions? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.NOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Modify an Azure Trahc Manager pro+le"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Modify a network security group (NSG)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Modify a DDoS protection plan"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Modify an Azure +rewall"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-network/security-overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 126,
      "original_number": "253",
      "question": "You have an Azure environment that contains 10 virtual networks and 100 virtual machines.You need to limit the amount of inbound trahc to all the Azure virtual networks.What should you create?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "one application security group (ASG)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "10 virtual network gateways"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "10 Azure ExpressRoute circuits"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "one Azure +rewall"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "You can restrict trahc to multiple virtual networks with a single Azure +rewall.Azure Firewall is a managed, cloud-based network security service that protects your Azure Virtual Network resources. It's a fully stateful+rewall as a service with built-in high availability and unrestricted cloud scalability.You can centrally create, enforce, and log application and network connectivity policies across subscriptions and virtual networks. AzureFirewall uses a static public IP address for your virtual network resources allowing outside +rewalls to identify trahc originating from yourvirtual network. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/+rewall/overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 127,
      "original_number": "254",
      "question": "This question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.Azure Key Vault is used to store secrets for Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) user accounts.Instructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select theanswer choice that makes the statement correct.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "No change is needed"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) administrative accounts"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Personally Identi+able Information (PII)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "server applications"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "Key Vault is designed to store con+guration secrets for server apps. It's not intended for storing data belonging to your app's users, and itshouldn't be used in the client-side part of an app. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/modules/manage-secrets-with-azure-key-vault/2-what-is-key-vault"
    },
    {
      "id": 128,
      "original_number": "255",
      "question": "Your company plans to automate the deployment of servers to Azure.Your manager is concerned that you may expose administrative credentials during the deployment.You need to recommend an Azure solution that encrypts the administrative credentials during the deployment.What should you include in the recommendation?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Key Vault"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Information Protection"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Security Center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/key-vault/key-vault-overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 129,
      "original_number": "256",
      "question": "You plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.You need to control the ports that devices on the Internet can use to access the virtual machines.What should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a network security group (NSG)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) role"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "an Azure Active Directory group"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Azure key vault"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "A network security group works like a +rewall. You can attach a network security group to a virtual network and/or individual subnets within thevirtual network.You can also attach a network security group to a network interface assigned to a virtual machine. You can use multiple network securitygroups within a virtual network to restrict trahc between resources such as virtual machines and subnets.You can +lter network trahc to and from Azure resources in an Azure virtual network with a network security group. A network security groupcontains security rules that allow or deny inbound network trahc to, or outbound network trahc from, several types of Azure resources. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-network/security-overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 130,
      "original_number": "259",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.Your Azure environment contains multiple Azure virtual machines.You need to ensure that a virtual machine named VM1 is accessible from the Internet over HTTP .Solution: You modify a network security group (NSG).Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-network/security-overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 131,
      "original_number": "260",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.Your Azure environment contains multiple Azure virtual machines.You need to ensure that a virtual machine named VM1 is accessible from the Internet over HTTP .Solution: You modify a DDoS protection plan.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "DDoS is a form of attack on a network resource. A DDoS protection plan is used to protect against DDoS attacks; it does not provideconnectivity to a virtual machine.To ensure that a virtual machine named VM1 is accessible from the Internet over HTTP , you need to modify a network security group or AzureFirewall. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-network/ddos-protection-overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 132,
      "original_number": "261",
      "question": "You need to collect and automatically analyze security events from Azure Active Directory (Azure AD).What should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Sentinel"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Synapse Analytics"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure AD Connect"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Key Vault"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/sentinel/overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 133,
      "original_number": "262",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.Your Azure environment contains multiple Azure virtual machines.You need to ensure that a virtual machine named VM1 is accessible from the Internet over HTTP .Solution: You modify an Azure +rewall.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Azure Firewall is a managed, cloud-based network security service that protects your Azure Virtual Network resources. It's a fully stateful+rewall as a service with built-in high availability and unrestricted cloud scalability.In this question, we need to add a rule to Azure Firewall to allow the connection to the virtual machine on port 80 (HTTP). | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/+rewall/overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 134,
      "original_number": "263",
      "question": "This question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.Azure Germany can be used by legal residents of Germany only.Instructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select theanswer choice that makes the statement correct.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "no change is needed"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "only enterprises that are registered in Germany"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "only enterprises that purchase their azure licenses from a partner based in Germany"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "any user or enterprise that requires its data to reside in Germany"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "Azure Germany is available to eligible customers and partners globally who intend to do business in the EU/EFTA, including the UnitedKingdom.Azure Germany offers a separate instance of Microsoft Azure services from within German datacenters. The datacenters are in two locations,Frankfurt/Main andMagdeburg. This placement ensures that customer data remains in Germany and that the datacenters connect to each other through a privatenetwork. All customer data is exclusively stored in those datacenters. A designated German company--the German data trustee--controlsaccess to customer data and the systems and infrastructure that hold customer data. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/germany/germany-welcome?toc=%2fazure%2fgermany%2ftoc.json"
    },
    {
      "id": 135,
      "original_number": "266",
      "question": "What should you use to evaluate whether your company's Azure environment meets regulatory requirements?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Service Health"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Knowledge Center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Security Center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "The advanced monitoring capabilities in Security Center lets you track and manage compliance and governance over time. The overallcompliance provides you with a measure of how much your subscriptions are compliant with policies associated with your workload. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/security-center/security-center-introCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 136,
      "original_number": "269",
      "question": "Which two types of customers are eligible to use Azure Government to develop a cloud solution? Each correct answer presents a completesolution.NOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a Canadian government contractor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a European government contractor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a United States government entity"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a United States government contractor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "a European government entity"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "DAzure Government is a cloud environment speci+cally built to meet compliance and security requirements for US government. This mission-critical cloud delivers breakthrough innovation to U.S. government customers and their partners. Azure Government applies to government atany level ג \"€from state and local governments to federal agencies including Department of Defense agencies.The key difference between Microsoft Azure and Microsoft Azure Government is that Azure Government is a sovereign cloud. It's a physicallyseparated instance of Azure, dedicated to U.S. government workloads only. It's built exclusively for government agencies and their solutionproviders. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/modules/intro-to-azure-government/2-what-is-azure-governmentCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 137,
      "original_number": "271",
      "question": "You need to ensure that when Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) users connect to Azure AD from the Internet by using an anonymous IP address,the users are prompted automatically to change their password.Which Azure service should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure AD Connect Health"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure AD Privileged Identity Management"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Advanced Threat Protection (ATP)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure AD Identity Protection"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "Azure AD Identity Protection includes two risk policies: sign-in risk policy and user risk policy. A sign-in risk represents the probability that agiven authentication request isn't authorized by the identity owner.There are several types of risk detection. One of them is Anonymous IP Address. This risk detection type indicates sign-ins from an anonymousIP address (for example, Tor browser or anonymous VPN). These IP addresses are typically used by actors who want to hide their logintelemetry (IP address, location, device, etc.) for potentially malicious intent.You can con+gure the sign-in risk policy to require that users change their password. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/active-directory/identity-protection/howto-sign-in-risk-policy"
    },
    {
      "id": 138,
      "original_number": "273",
      "question": "To what should an application connect to retrieve security tokens?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "an Azure Storage account"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a certi+cate store"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Azure key vault"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "Key Vault is designed to store con+guration secrets for server apps.Incorrect Answers:A: An Azure Storage account is used to store data. It is not used to store secrets for applications.B: Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) is a centralized identity provider in the cloud that authenticates users and provides access tokens to them.It is not used for applications. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/modules/manage-secrets-with-azure-key-vault/2-what-is-key-vault"
    },
    {
      "id": 139,
      "original_number": "274",
      "question": "Your network contains an Active Directory forest. The forest contains 5,000 user accounts.Your company plans to migrate all network resources to Azure and to decommission the on-premises data center.You need to recommend a solution to minimize the impact on users after the planned migration.What should you recommend?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Implement Azure Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Sync all the Active Directory user accounts to Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Instruct all users to change their password"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Create a guest user account in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) for each user"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "To migrate to Azure and decommission the on-premises data center, you would need to create the 5,000 user accounts in Azure ActiveDirectory. The easy way to do this is to sync all the Active Directory user accounts to Azure Active Directory (Azure AD). You can even sync theirpasswords to further minimize the impact on users.The tool you would use to sync the accounts is Azure AD Connect. The Azure Active Directory Connect synchronization services (Azure ADConnect sync) is a main component of Azure AD Connect. It takes care of all the operations that are related to synchronize identity databetween your on-premises environment andAzure AD. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/active-directory/hybrid/how-to-connect-sync-whatisCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 140,
      "original_number": "277",
      "question": "You have a resource group named RG1.You need to prevent the creation of virtual machines in RG1. The solution must ensure that other objects can be created in RG1.What should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a lock"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure role"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a tag"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Azure policy"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/governance/policy/overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 141,
      "original_number": "278",
      "question": "You have an Azure subscription and 100 Windows 10 devices.You need to ensure that only users whose devices have the latest security patches installed can access Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)-integrated applications.What should you implement?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a conditional access policy"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Bastion"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Firewall"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Policy"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/active-directory/conditional-access/concept-conditional-access-policiesCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 142,
      "original_number": "279",
      "question": "What can Azure Information Protection encrypt?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "network trahc"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "documents and email messages"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "an Azure Storage account"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Azure SQL database"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/information-protection/what-is-information-protection"
    },
    {
      "id": 143,
      "original_number": "280",
      "question": "What should you use to evaluate whether your company's Azure environment meets regulatory requirements?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "the Knowledge Center website"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "the Advisor blade from the Azure portal"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Compliance Manager from the Service Trust Portal"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "the Solutions blade from the Azure portal"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Compliance Manager in the Service Trust Portal is a workjow-based risk assessment tool that helps you track, assign, and verify yourorganization's regulatory compliance activities related to Microsoft Cloud services, such as Microsoft 365, Dynamics 365, and Azure. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-365/compliance/get-started-with-service-trust-portal?view=o365-worldwideCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 144,
      "original_number": "282",
      "question": "You have an Azure subscription.Where will you +nd details on the personal data collected by Microsoft, how Microsoft uses the data, and what the data is used for?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "the Data Protection Addendum"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "the Microsoft Online Services Terms"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "the Microsoft Privacy Statement"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Security Center"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "The Microsoft Privacy Statement explains the personal data Microsoft processes, how Microsoft processes it, and for what purposes. Yourapplicable ServicesAgreement or the Preview Supplemental Terms may specify lesser or different privacy measures for some Preview services. | Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/support/legal"
    },
    {
      "id": 145,
      "original_number": "290",
      "question": "What should you use to evaluate whether your company's Azure environment meets regulatory requirements?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Service Health"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Knowledge Center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Microsoft Defender for Cloud"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Microsoft Defender for Cloud helps streamline the process for meeting regulatory compliance requirements, using the regulatory compliancedashboard. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/defender-for-cloud/regulatory-compliance-dashboardCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 146,
      "original_number": "293",
      "question": "Your company has an Azure subscription that contains resources in several regions.You need to create the Azure resource that must be used to meet the policy requirement.What should you create?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a read-only lock"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure policy"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a management group"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a reservation"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/governance/policy/overviewCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 147,
      "original_number": "294",
      "question": "This question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.From Azure Cloud Shell, you can track your company's regulatory standards and regulations, such as ISO 27001.Instructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed.` If the statement is incorrect, select theanswer choice that makes the statement correct.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "No change is needed."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "the Microsoft Cloud Partner Portal"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Compliance Manager"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "the Trust Center"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Microsoft Compliance Manager (Preview) is a free workjow-based risk assessment tool that lets you track, assign, and verify regulatorycompliance activities related to Microsoft cloud services. Azure Cloud Shell, on the other hand, is an interactive, authenticated, browser-accessible shell for managing Azure resources. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-365/compliance/compliance-manager-overview"
    },
    {
      "id": 148,
      "original_number": "304",
      "question": "Your company plans to migrate all on-premises data to Azure.You need to identify whether Azure complies with the company's regional requirements.What should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "the Knowledge Center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Marketplace"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "the MyApps portal"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "the Trust Center"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "Azure has more than 90 compliance certi+cations, including over 50 speci+c to global regions and countries, such as the US, the EuropeanUnion, Germany,Japan, the United Kingdom, India and China.You can view a list of compliance certi+cations in the Trust Center to determine whether Azure meets your regional requirements. | Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/overview/trusted-cloud/compliance"
    },
    {
      "id": 149,
      "original_number": "309",
      "question": "What is guaranteed in an Azure Service Level Agreement (SLA) for virtual machines?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "uptime"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "feature availability"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "bandwidth"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "performance"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/support/legal/sla/summary/https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/support/legal/sla/virtual-machines/v1_9"
    },
    {
      "id": 150,
      "original_number": "311",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.Your company plans to purchase an Azure subscription.The company's support policy states that the Azure environment must provide an option to access support engineers by phone or email.You need to recommend which support plan meets the support policy requirement.Solution: Recommend a Basic support plan.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "The Basic support plan does not have any technical support for engineers.Access to Support Engineers via email or phone is available in the following support plans: Premier, Professional Direct and standard. | Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/support/plans"
    },
    {
      "id": 151,
      "original_number": "312",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.Your company plans to purchase an Azure subscription.The company's support policy states that the Azure environment must provide an option to access support engineers by phone or email.You need to recommend which support plan meets the support policy requirement.Solution: Recommend a Standard support plan.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "The Standard, Professional Direct, and Premier support plans have technical support for engineers via email and phone. | Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/support/plans"
    },
    {
      "id": 152,
      "original_number": "313",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.Your company plans to purchase an Azure subscription.The company's support policy states that the Azure environment must provide an option to access support engineers by phone or email.You need to recommend which support plan meets the support policy requirement.Solution: Recommend a Premier support plan.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "The Standard, Professional Direct, and Premier support plans have technical support for engineers via email and phone. | Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/support/plans"
    },
    {
      "id": 153,
      "original_number": "314",
      "question": "Your company plans to request an architectural review of an Azure environment from Microsoft.The company currently has a Basic support plan.You need to recommend a new support plan for the company. The solution must minimize costs.Which support plan should you recommend?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Premier"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Developer"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Professional Direct"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Standard"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "The Premier support plan provides customer speci+c architectural support such as design reviews, performance tuning, con+guration andimplementation assistance delivered by Microsoft Azure technical specialists. | Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/support/plans"
    },
    {
      "id": 154,
      "original_number": "316",
      "question": "What is required to use Azure Cost Management?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a Dev/Test subscription"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Software Assurance"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "an Enterprise Agreement (EA)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a pay-as-you-go subscription"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Azure customers with an Azure Enterprise Agreement (EA), Microsoft Customer Agreement (MCA), or Microsoft Partner Agreement (MPA) canuse Azure CostManagement.Cost management is the process of effectively planning and controlling costs involved in your business. Cost management tasks are normallyperformed by +nance, management, and app teams. Azure Cost Management + Billing helps organizations plan with cost in mind. It also helpsto analyze costs effectively and take action to optimize cloud spending. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-gb/azure/cost-management/overview-cost-mgtCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 155,
      "original_number": "318",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.Your company plans to purchase an Azure subscription.The company's support policy states that the Azure environment must provide an option to access support engineers by phone or email.You need to recommend which support plan meets the support policy requirement.Solution: Recommend a Professional Direct support plan.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "The Basic support plan does not have any technical support for engineers.The Developer support plan has only technical support for engineers via email.The Standard, Professional Direct, and Premier support plans have technical support for engineers via email and phone. | Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/support/plans"
    },
    {
      "id": 156,
      "original_number": "319",
      "question": "Your company has a Software Assurance agreement that includes Microsoft SQL Server licenses.You plan to deploy SQL Server on Azure virtual machines.What should you do to minimize licensing costs for the deployment?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Deallocate the virtual machines during off hours."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Use Azure Hybrid Bene+t."
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Con+gure Azure Cost Management budgets."
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Use Azure reservations."
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Azure Hybrid Bene+t is a licensing bene+t that helps you to signi+cantly reduce the costs of running your workloads in the cloud. It works byletting you use your on-premises Software Assurance-enabled Windows Server and SQL Server licenses on Azure. | Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/pricing/hybrid-bene+t"
    },
    {
      "id": 157,
      "original_number": "320",
      "question": "Your company has 10 departments.The company plans to implement an Azure environment.You need to ensure that each department can use a different payment option for the Azure services it consumes.What should you create for each department?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a reservation"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a subscription"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a resource group"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a container instance"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cost-management-billing/manage/create-subscriptionCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 158,
      "original_number": "327",
      "question": "Which statement accurately describes the Modern Lifecycle Policy for Azure services?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Microsoft provides mainstream support for a service for +ve years."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Microsoft provides a minimum of 12 months' notice before ending support for a service."
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "After a service is made generally available, Microsoft provides support for the service for a minimum of four years."
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "When a service is retired, you can purchase extended support for the service for up to +ve years."
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "For products governed by the Modern Lifecycle Policy, Microsoft will provide a minimum of 12 months' noti+cation prior to ending support if nosuccessor product or service is offered ג \"€excluding free services or preview releases. | Reference: https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/30881/modern-lifecycle-policyCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 159,
      "original_number": "332",
      "question": "Your company has an Azure subscription that contains the following unused resources:✑ 20 user accounts in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)✑ Five groups in Azure AD✑ 10 public IP addresses✑ 10 network interfacesYou need to reduce the Azure costs for the company.Which unused resources should you remove?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "the network interfaces"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "the public IP addresses"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "the groups"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "the user accounts"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "You are charged for public IP addresses. Therefore, deleting unused public IP addresses will reduce the Azure costs. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/advisor/advisor-cost-recommendations#reduce-costs-by-deleting-or-recon+guring-idle-virtual-network-gatewaysCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 160,
      "original_number": "337",
      "question": "Who can use the Azure Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) calculator?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "billing readers for an Azure subscription only"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "owners for an Azure subscription only"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "anyone"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "all users who have an account in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) that is linked to an Azure subscription only"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "You don't need an Azure subscription to work with the TCO Calculator. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/modules/plan-manage-azure-costs/2-compare-costs-tco-calculatorCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 161,
      "original_number": "339",
      "question": "Which task can you perform by using Azure Advisor?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Integrate Active Directory and Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Estimate the costs of an Azure solution."
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Con+rm that Azure subscription security follows best practices."
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Evaluate which on-premises resources can be migrated to Azure."
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Reference: https://blog.pragmaticworks.com/what-is-azure-advi-sor#:~:text=Microsoft%20de+nes%20Azure%20Advisor%20as,solutions%20based%20on%20that%20dataCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 162,
      "original_number": "341",
      "question": "You have an Azure application that uses the services shown in the following table. How should you calculate the composite SLA for the application?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "0.999 * 0.9999 = 0.9989001 = 99.89001%"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "0.999 / 0.9999 = 0.9991 = 99.91%"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Max(0.999, 0.9999) = 0.9999 = 99.99%"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Min(0.999, 0.9999) = 0.999 = 99.9%"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Composite SLAs involve multiple services supporting an application, each with differing levels of availability. For example, consider an AppService web app that writes to Azure SQL Database. At the time of this writing, these Azure services have the following SLAs:✑ App Service web apps = 99.95%✑ SQL Database = 99.99%What is the maximum downtime you would expect for this application? If either service fails, the whole application fails. The probability of eachservice failing is independent, so the composite SLA for this application is 99.95% ֳ —99.99% = 99.94%. That's lower than the individual SLAs,which isn't surprising because an application that relies on multiple services has more potential failure points. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/architecture/reliability/requirements#understand-service-level-agreementsCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 163,
      "original_number": "348",
      "question": "You have 1,000 virtual machines hosted on the Hyper-V hosts in a data center.You plan to migrate all the virtual machines to an Azure pay-as-you-go subscription.You need to identify which expenditure model to use for the planned Azure solution.Which expenditure model should you identify?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "scalable"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "operational"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "elastic"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "capital"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "One of the major changes that you will face when you move from on-premises cloud to the public cloud is the switch from capital expenditure(buying hardware) to operating expenditure (paying for service as you use it). This switch also requires more careful management of yourcosts. The bene+t of the cloud is that you can fundamentally and positively affect the cost of a service you use by merely shutting down orresizing it when it's not needed. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/architecture/cloud-adoption/appendix/azure-scaffoldCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 164,
      "original_number": "351",
      "question": "Which Service Level Agreement (SLA) is provided for Azure services in public preview?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Each service de+nes its own SLA"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "The SLA will be 99%"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "The SLA will be 1% less than the general availability (GA) SLA"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "The SLA will be 99.95%"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 165,
      "original_number": "355",
      "question": "What is the longest term you can purchase for Azure Reserved VM instances?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "one year"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "+ve years"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "four years"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "three years"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "Azure Reservations help you save money by committing to one-year or three-year plans for multiple products. Committing allows you to get adiscount on the resources you use. Reservations can signi+cantly reduce your resource costs by up to 72% from pay-as-you-go prices. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cost-management-billing/reservations/save-compute-costs-reservationsCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 166,
      "original_number": "357",
      "question": "Your company has 10 ohces. You plan to generate several billing reports from the Azure portal. Each report will contain the Azure resourceutilization of each ohce.Which Azure Resource Manager feature should you use before you generate the reports?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "tags"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "templates"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "locks"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "policies"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "You can use resource tags to 'label' Azure resources. Tags are metadata elements attached to resources. Tags consist of pairs of key/valuestrings. In this question, we would tag each resource with a tag to identify each ohce. For example: Location = Ohce1. When all Azureresources are tagged, you can generate reports to list all resources based on the value of the tag. For example: All resources used by Ohce1. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cloud-adoption-framework/decision-guides/resource-tagging"
    },
    {
      "id": 167,
      "original_number": "359",
      "question": "This question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.If Microsoft plans to end support for an Azure service that does NOT have a successor service, Microsoft will provide noti+cation at least 12months before.Instructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select theanswer choice that makes the statement correct.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "No change is needed."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "6 months"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "90 days"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "30 days"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "The Modern Lifecycle Policy covers products and services that are serviced and supported continuously. For products governed by the ModernLifecycle Policy,Microsoft will provide a minimum of 12 months' noti+cation prior to ending support if no successor product or service is offeredג\"€excludingfree services or preview releases. | Reference: https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/30881Community"
    },
    {
      "id": 168,
      "original_number": "362",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.Your company has an Azure subscription that contains the following unused resources:✑ 20 user accounts in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)✑ Five groups in Azure AD✑ 10 public IP addresses✑ 10 network interfacesYou need to reduce the Azure costs for the company.Solution: You remove the unused network interfaces.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "You are not charged for unused network interfaces. Therefore, deleting unused network interfaces will not reduce the Azure costs for thecompany. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/advisor/advisor-cost-recommendations#reduce-costs-by-deleting-or-recon+guring-idle-virtual-network-gatewaysCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 169,
      "original_number": "363",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.Your company has an Azure subscription that contains the following unused resources:✑ 20 user accounts in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)Five groups in Azure AD - ✑ 10 public IP addresses✑ 10 network interfacesYou need to reduce the Azure costs for the company.Solution: You remove the unused public IP addresses.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "You are charged for public IP addresses. Therefore, deleting unused public IP addresses will reduce the Azure costs. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/advisor/advisor-cost-recommendations#reduce-costs-by-deleting-or-recon+guring-idle-virtual-network-gatewaysCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 170,
      "original_number": "364",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.Your company has an Azure subscription that contains the following unused resources:✑ 20 user accounts in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)✑ Five groups in Azure AD✑ 10 public IP addresses✑ 10 network interfacesYou need to reduce the Azure costs for the company.Solution: You remove the unused user accounts.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "You are not charged for user accounts. Therefore, deleting unused user accounts will not reduce the Azure costs for the company. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/advisor/advisor-cost-recommendations#reduce-costs-by-deleting-or-recon+guring-idle-virtual-network-gatewaysCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 171,
      "original_number": "367",
      "question": "This question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.A support plan solution that gives you best practice information, health status and noti+cations, and 24/7 access to billing information at thelowest possible cost is a Standard support plan.Instructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select theanswer choice that makes the statement correct.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "No change is needed"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Developer"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Basic"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Premier"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "A basic support plan provides:✑ 24x7 access to billing and subscription support, online self-help, documentation, whitepapers, and support forums✑ Best practices: Access to full set of Azure Advisor recommendations✑ Health Status and Noti+cations: Access to personalized Service Health Dashboard & Health API | Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/support/plans"
    },
    {
      "id": 172,
      "original_number": "368",
      "question": "In which Azure support plans can you open a new support request?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Premier and Professional Direct only"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Premier, Professional Direct, and Standard only"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Premier, Professional Direct, Standard, and Developer only"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Premier, Professional Direct, Standard, Developer, and Basic"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "You can submit support request tickets in the following plans: Premier, Professional Direct, Standard, Developer, and Basic. | Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/support/plans"
    },
    {
      "id": 173,
      "original_number": "369",
      "question": "This question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.You can create an Azure support request from support.microsoft.com.Instructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed.` If the statement is incorrect, select theanswer choice that makes the statement correct.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "No change is needed."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "the Azure portal"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "the Knowledge Center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "the Security & Compliance admin center"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "You can create an Azure support request from the Help and Support blade in the Azure portal or from the context menu of an Azure resource inthe Support +Troubleshooting section. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-supportability/how-to-create-azure-support-requestCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 174,
      "original_number": "370",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution thatmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.After you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.Your company has an Azure subscription that contains the following unused resources:✑ 20 user accounts in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)✑ Five groups in Azure AD✑ 10 public IP addresses✑ 10 network interfacesYou need to reduce the Azure costs for the company.Solution: You remove the unused groups.Does this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "You are not charged for Azure Active Directory Groups. Therefore, deleting unused groups will not reduce your Azure costs. | Reference: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/advisor/advisor-cost-recommendations#reduce-costs-by-deleting-or-recon+guring-idle-virtual-network-gatewaysCommunity"
    },
    {
      "id": 175,
      "original_number": "371",
      "question": "This question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.The Azure Standard support plan is the lowest cost option to receive 24x7 access to support engineers by phone.Instructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select theanswer choice that makes the statement correct.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "No change is needed"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Developer"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Basic"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Professional Direct"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "The Basic support plan is free so is therefore the cheapest. The Developer support plan is the cheapest paid-for support plan. The order ofsupport plans in terms of cost ranging from the cheapest to most expensive is: Basic, Developer, Standard, Professional Direct, Premier.However, 24/7 access to technical support by email and phone is only available for Standard, Professional Direct, Premier plans. | Reference: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/support/plans"
    },
    {
      "id": 176,
      "original_number": "374",
      "question": "You need to compare a company's cloud usage to industry standard best practices.What should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Monitor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Service Health"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Application Insights in Azure Monitor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 177,
      "original_number": "375",
      "question": "You need to start Azure Cloud Shell.What should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "the Azure portal"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Command-Line Interface (CLI)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure PowerShell"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Azure Resource Manager (ARM) template"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 178,
      "original_number": "377",
      "question": "What enables a cloud service to adapt quickly to changing requirements?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "high availability"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "predictability"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "manageability"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "agility"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 179,
      "original_number": "378",
      "question": "What is an example of vertical scaling in a cloud environment?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "adding an additional CPU to an existing Azure virtual machine"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "adding an additional Azure virtual machine"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "adding an additional Azure Virtual Desktop session host"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "adding an additional Azure App Service instance automatically"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 180,
      "original_number": "381",
      "question": "What additional resource is required by an Azure virtual machine?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a virtual network"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a service endpoint"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Firewall"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a public IP address"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 181,
      "original_number": "384",
      "question": "What is used to grant permission to Azure Virtual Desktop resources?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "tags"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "role-based access control (RBAC) roles"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "resource groups"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "application security groups"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 182,
      "original_number": "389",
      "question": "Which cloud service model minimizes the management responsibility of a customer?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "infrastructure as a service (IaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "platform as a service (PaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "software as a service (SaaS)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 183,
      "original_number": "398",
      "question": "You have an Azure web app.You need to manage the settings of the web app from an iPhone.What are two Azure management tools that you can use? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.NOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Windows PowerShell"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Cloud Shell"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "the Azure portal"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Storage Explorer"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 184,
      "original_number": "401",
      "question": "What should you use to prevent trahc from an Azure virtual network from being routed to an Azure Storage account via the internet?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a network security group (NSG)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a public endpoint"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure VPN Gateway"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a service endpoint"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 185,
      "original_number": "402",
      "question": "Which service can replace a resource lock automatically if the lock is removed?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Information Protection (AIP)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Blueprints"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Backup"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 186,
      "original_number": "405",
      "question": "You plan to collect and analyze event details for +ve Azure virtual machines.You need to run queries to compare the event details collected from all the virtual machines.Which two tools should you use? Each correct answer presents part of the solution.NOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Service Health"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Service Bus"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Monitor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "Log Analytics"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 187,
      "original_number": "407",
      "question": "What should you use to track the costs of Azure resources?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Quickstart templates"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "tags"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "budgets"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "usage and quotas"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 188,
      "original_number": "408",
      "question": "You have an Azure subscription.You plan to create a virtual machine.Where will the virtual machine be placed in Azure?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "In a storage account"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "In a resource group"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "In an administrative unit"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "In an application group"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 189,
      "original_number": "411",
      "question": "You plan to reduce ongoing Azure expenditures.You need to identify which factors affect the costs of a resource.Which three factors should you identify? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.NOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "the volume of outbound data"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "the volume of inbound data"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "the service tier"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "the Azure region"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "the type of processed data"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 190,
      "original_number": "412",
      "question": "Your company has an Azure subscription that contains several resources.You need to identify which department is responsible for the cost of each resource.What should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "budgets"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "alerts"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "tags"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 191,
      "original_number": "420",
      "question": "You have on-premises servers that run Windows Server.What should you implement to manage the servers by using the Azure portal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Arc"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Docker"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "role-based access control (RBAC)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 192,
      "original_number": "423",
      "question": "You have a web app that runs in Azure.You need to identify the amount of time it takes for web pages to load in a user's browser.What should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Monitor alerts"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Application Insights in Azure Monitor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Log Analytics"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Network Watcher"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 193,
      "original_number": "425",
      "question": "What should a desktop application use to interact with Azure and manage resources?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "APIs"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Resource Manager (ARM) templates"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Command-Line Interface (CLI)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Cloud Shell"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 194,
      "original_number": "429",
      "question": "Which two features or services can be integrated with Azure Monitor? Each correct answer presents part of the solution.NOTE: Each correct answer is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure status"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Application Insights"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Log Analytics"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "Azure Service Health"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 195,
      "original_number": "430",
      "question": "What provides a uni+ed way to project and manage non-Azure resources in Azure Resource Manager (ARM)?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Migrate"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure AD Connect"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Arc"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Front Door"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 196,
      "original_number": "433",
      "question": "Your company has an Azure subscription and three business units.You plan to deploy new resources for each business unit.You need to ensure that the new resources are deployed by using a repeatable and reliable method that applies the same con+gurations to eachresource.What should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Policy"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Arc"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a resource group"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Resource Manager (ARM) templates"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 197,
      "original_number": "437",
      "question": "In the software as a service (SaaS) cloud service, which responsibility is shared between Microsoft and the customer?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "identity and directory infrastructure management"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "application management"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "information and data management"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "operating system updates"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 198,
      "original_number": "438",
      "question": "Where does Azure Monitor store event data?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "an Azure Blob Storage account"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Storage Queue"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure SQL Database"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a Log Analytics workspace"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 199,
      "original_number": "443",
      "question": "An Azure administrator plans to run a PowerShell script that creates Azure resources.You need to recommend which computer con+guration to use to run the script.Which three computers can run the script? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.NOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a computer that runs Windows 11 and has the Azure CLI tools installed"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a computer that runs Linux and has the Azure CLI tools installed"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a computer that runs macOS and has PowerShell Core 6.0 installed"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a computer that runs Chrome OS and uses Azure Cloud Shell"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "a computer that runs Windows 10 and has the Azure PowerShell module installed"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 200,
      "original_number": "445",
      "question": "In the infrastructure as a service (IaaS) cloud service model, which two components are the responsibility of the cloud service provider? Eachcorrect answer presents a complete solution.NOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "the con+guration and maintenance of storage"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "the installation and con+guration of the operating system"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "maintaining the hardware"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "the network con+guration"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "physical security of the datacenter infrastructure"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 201,
      "original_number": "450",
      "question": "You have an Azure Storage account named storage1.You need to ensure that containers can be created in, but not deleted from, storage1.What should you do?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Create a ReadOnly lock for storage1."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Create a delete lock for storage1."
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Enable container soft delete."
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Enable blob soft delete."
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 202,
      "original_number": "451",
      "question": "You have an Azure subscription.You need to use Azure Cloud Shell to run a deployment script.What should you use to access Cloud Shell?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Resource Manager (ARM)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Microsoft Visual Studio"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a Windows command prompt"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a web browser"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 203,
      "original_number": "454",
      "question": "You need to migrate an on-premises server by using a lift-and-shift migration.To which type of cloud service should you migrate?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "infrastructure as a service (IaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "software as a service (SaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "platform as a service (PaaS)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    }
  ]
}